Oh.
Hick.
It's disgusting!
I don't like licorice because it's like salty and sweet in one, and it's like "berry" and ...
- "Bearing"?!
- A "berry" taste.
Wondering what it is.
Ah ... you have not understood the good of life.
Or maybe a snail ... a slimy snail mixed with pudding.
So, is it only our children who do not like licorice?
How is it at your house, if you have children at home or if you are a child and watch.
Do you like licorice or not?
Comment below.
- Comment.
- Gladly.
Very.
♪ zero, zero, zero, zero ... ♪
- No.
- Yes.
It was good.
- Not taste!
- Oooh ... so synthetic.
The yum police.
- I give 5 points.
- Oh!
Good.
I give 3.5.
- Five fives.
- Oh!
They roll around in my skull.
I give 4 points.
"Karl Fazer - Maitosuklaa"
It is thus milk chocolate.
Finnish equivalent of Marabou.
- Though a little more boring.
- Do you think.